Guide to the NYU Abu Dhabi Publications and Ephemera Collection AD.RG.002.1-1
NYU Abu Dhabi, Archives and Special Collections
NYU Abu Dhabi Publications and Ephemera
2010-2022
NYU Abu Dhabi, Archives and Special Collections
AD.RG.002.1-1
5.0 Linear Feet in 9 legal-sized document boxes, and 3 oversize folders.
The NYU Abu Dhabi Publications and Ephemera collection consists of published bulletins, curricula guides, brochures, research reports, commemencement programs, class yearbooks, events catalogs and calendars, faculty and student journals, and a few commemorative artifacts, which document academic and community life across the NYU Abu Dhabi campus, including research achievements, from 2010 - present.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in six series.
Admissions and Recruitment
Students
Research and Achievements
Course and Curricula Information
Campus departments, programs, events, journals
Artifacts
Scope and Contents
NYU Abu Dhabi Publications and Ephemera consist of published bulletins, curricula guides, brochures, research reports, commemencement programs, class yearbooks, events catalogs and calendars, faculty and student journals, and a few commemorative artifacts, which document academic and community life across the NYU Abu Dhabi campus, including research achievements, from 2010 - present. When available, two copies of each publication have been retained and are preserved as part of this collection.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Materials in this Record Group have been acquired over time from a variety of sources, donated to the library, picked up by Library staff at events, donated or transferred from outgoing staff upon their exit or other offices, and transferred as part of an annual routine transfer (such as Bulletins transferred by the Registrar).
NYU Abu Dhabi; Universities
- Admissions
  Scope and Contents
  Publications and ephemera related to the University's efforts to recruit faculty and students.
  - Admissions: General Material, 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Admissions: General Material, 2012-2013 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Admissions: General Material, 2012-2013 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Admissions: Recruitment Materials, General and Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Students
  This series of publications constitutes materials pertaining to the students of NYU Abu Dhabi, including class yearbooks, Capstone Project summaries and festival programs, commencement exercises, and Ma'a Salama materials. Arranged alphabetically, then by year. Note: Capstone Archives are collected and administered in a separate record group.
  - Arts and Humanities Capstone Festival Program, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Arts and Humanities Capstone Festival Group Exhibition, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Arts and Humanities Capstone Festival Program, 2017 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Capstone Project: Summary, Class of 2015 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Capstone Project: Summary, Class of 2017 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Capstone Projects, various programs, 2017 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Class of 2014 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Inaugural Commencement Exercises, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Saariya, Class of 2014 Yearbook (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Marhaba, 2015 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - This is the Class of 2015 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Class of 2015 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Ma'a Salama, 2015 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Exercises, 2015 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Commencement 2015: Printed Communications (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - This is the Class of 2016 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Class of 2016 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Life Beyond Saadiyat, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - This is the Class of 2017 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Class of 2017 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - This is the Class of 2018 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Class of 2014 - Class of 2018 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Research and Achievements, 2014-2018
  Publications that highlight NYU Abu Dhabi research achievements, including annual research reports and research conference publications. Arranged chronologically.
  - Research Report, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Research: Local Relevance, Global Perspective, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Research Report, 2013-2014 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Annual Research Conference, February 22-24, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Annual Research Conference, February 28-March 1, 2015 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Research, 2015-2016 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Highlights: UAE Impact, 2015-2016 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Research 2016 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Research 2017 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - UAE Highlights, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - UAE Highlights, 2017-2018 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Research Conference, 2018 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Course and Curricula Information, 2010-2019
  Published descriptions of courses and the core curricula offered at NYU Abu Dhabi. Arranged chronologically. Other related materials include web-based course descriptions, which are preserved in New York as part of the NYU University Archives. Note: is anticipated that these publications will transition to electronic only after the 2020-2021 academic year.
  - Preview of Academic Programs, 2010-2011 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Bulletin 2010-2011 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Bulletin 2012-2013 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Bulletin 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Bulletin 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Bulletin 2015-2016 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Bulletin 2016-2017 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Bulletin 2017-2018 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Bulletin 2018-2019 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Bulletin 2019-2020 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Core Curriculum User Guide, 2016-2017 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Core Curriculum User Guide, 2017-2018 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Core Curriculum User Guide, 2018-2019 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Core Curriculum User Guide, 2019-2020 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Core Curriculum User Guide, 2021-2022 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    General
    *includes appendix with stickers
- Campus departments, programs, events, journals, 2014-2019
  Organized alphabetically by unit or event, this series consists of published material that promotes, documents and reflects the activities and special events of a variety of NYUAD programs, including conferences, academic programs, concerts and performances, exhibitions, and interdisciplinary published works.
  - Arts Center, 2015-2016 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Arts Center: Seasons, 2016-2019 (Map-case 1.C)
  - Mixed/Various Programs, 2014 - (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Institute, 2009-2014 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - NYUAD Institute: Year in Review, 2015-2016 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - NYUAD Institute: Year in Review, 2016-2017 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - NYUAD Institute: Year in Review, 2017-2018 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - NYUAD Institute: 5 Years (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - NYUAD Institute: 10 Years (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Project Space, 2015-2016 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - The Real AD Show, 2013 - (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - The Sheikh Mohamed Bin Zayed Scholars Program [brochure], 2012-2013 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - The Sheikh Mohamed Bin Zayed Scholars Program: Five Years of Reflections and Memories, 2013 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - The Sheikh Mohamed Bin Zayed Scholars Program: Celebrating A Decade of Excellence, 2018 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Theater Program, 2012-2015 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Journals (NYUAD): Analysis and Impression, Fall 2013 (Box 9)
  - Journals (NYUAD): Airport Road, A Journal of Student Creative Work, Issues 01-08, 2014-2018 (Box 9)
  - Journals (NYUAD): Electra Street, A Journal of the Arts and Humanities, Issues 01, 02, 2014-2015 (Box 9)
  - Journals (NYUAD): Exit 11, A Journal of the First Year Writing Seminar, 2016 (Box 9)
  - Journals (NYUAD): Food in the Global Kitchen: J-Term 2014 (Box 9)
  - Journals (NYUAD): A New Look At the Heritage, History and Memory in the UAE, Spring 2014 (Box 9)
  - Journals (NYUAD): New York University Abu Dhabi Journal of Social Sciences: Showcase of Exemplary Student Works, Fall 2013 (Box 9)
  - Urbanism of Hamdan Street, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Artifacts
  Although 3-D objects and physical artifacts are not generally collected by the Archives, some materials such as t-shirts, pins, buttons and other physical promotional materials are part of the collection.
  - Capstone Arts Festival Tee Shirt, 2017 (Box 10)